

ABOUT ME

With over 6 years of experience, I'm a highly creative and knowledgeable Graphic Designer with a strong background in developing and executing visual design concepts. I have a proven track record of increasing website traffic, reducing design time, and increasing brand recognition and engagement.

EDUCATION

BA in Multimedia 2014-16

Arena Animation RT Nagar

PUC 2012-14

Reva Independent PU college Kattigenahalli

SSLC 2010-11

Sterling English Residential School Kadiyarapanahalli 562149

ABOUT ME

BABU

+91 90368 82318

goldenkights@gmail.com

B.K Halli, Bangalore North Tq- 562 149

MADHAN

CREATIVE DESIGNER

EXPERIENCE

Team Lead Creative Designer Present

Kites Senior Care

Freelance Designer 2021-23

Dr. Reddys, TVS, Pepsi co, Springer Nature, FinStep, LAM, Capitaland

Creative Designer-Media Marketing 2018-21

Elmeasure India Pvt. Ltd.

Graphic Designer 2017-18

SLRT [Shree Lakshmi Ranganatha Tradelines]

ACHIEVEMENTS

2008 STATE LEVEL SKETCHING 2010 STATE LEVEL SKETCHING

SKILLS

LANGUAGES

English	1111111
Kannada	1111111
Hindi	111111

Software

CorelDraw	ı	ı	ı	ı	ı	ı	0
Photoshop	ı	ı	ı	ı	ı	ı	1
illustrator	ı	ı	ı		0	ı	0
After Effects	ı	ı					1
indesign	ı	ı	ı	ı	ı	ı	0
Blender	ı	ı	ı		0	1	